onemotoring.com.sg 2011-11-01

# ONE.MOTORING - Privacy Statement

### ONE.MOTORING PORTAL PRIVACY AGREEMENT

NCS ("the Company") takes your privacy seriously. The Company will not collect personally identifiable information about you when you visit this web site ("this Web Site") or use any of the Company's services provided on this Web Site unless you choose to provide that information to the Company.

Kindly view the MSI Global Pte Ltd ("MSI") Privacy Statement when you are using LTA Regulatory Applications on this website.

### WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This Privacy Policy covers the Company's treatment of personally identifiable information that the Company collects when you are on this Web Site and when you use the Company's services. This policy does not describe information collection policies on other sites, including those linked to or from the Company.

### ACCOUNTABILITY 

We are responsible for all personal data collected. All personal data collected will be used and processed fairly and lawfully while in our possession or custody. We ensure you that we are accountable for our organisation's compliance to our Privacy Policy. 

### SPECIFIYING PURPOSES

Personal data collected, will not be used for a new purpose unless we obtain consent from you. We are the sole owner of any personally identifiable information collected on this site and we collect personally identifiable information for the sole purpose of registering you for our web site.

### LIMITING COLLECTION

Only necessary personal data is collected from you. Both the amount and the type of data collected shall be limited to that which is necessary to enable the provision of website services on this website.

### TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

The Company does not collect any personally identifiable information about you other than information that you affirmatively choose to submit to us, such as your NRIC number, address, e-mail address and name. The Company also automatically collects aggregate information about the use of this Web Site, including which pages are most frequently visited, how many visitors this Web Site receives daily, and how long visitors stay on each page.

###   
COOKIES

When you visit this Web Site, a "cookie" will be sent to your computer. A cookie is a piece of data that identifies you as a unique user. The Company uses cookies on this Web Site to improve the quality of the Company's services and to understand the user base of this Web Site better. The Company does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how users search.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please note, however, that some parts of the services offered by the Company on this Web Site may not function properly if you refuse cookies.

### USE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

The personally identifiable information that the Company collects from and about you may be used to provide the services offered by the Company on this Web Site such as sending e-mail-based newsletters and other information to you as you request and to notify you from time to time about services offered by the Company or other entities associated with The Company. The Company may monitor your use of this Web Site, and may freely use and disclose any information and materials received from you or collected through your use of this Web Site for such purposes as the Company may deem appropriate, including but not limited to the purposes set out herein.

### ACCURACY

All personal information collected is accurate based on the information which was originally submitted. We do not maintain duplicate copies of personal information in different systems.

### SAFEGUARDS

Appropriate security safeguards are in place to protect personal data against unauthorised access, misuse, disclosure, copying, use, alteration, accidental loss or theft, destruction or damage. Only authorised personnel have access to our systems.

### SHARING OF INFORMATION

The Company may disclose information about you if the Company in its discretion decides that the Company has a good-faith belief that the Company is required to do so by law or legal process, to respond to claims, or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company or others. 

### OPENNESS

Our Privacy Policy is displayed on the web site and the policy is set out in the same language medium as the web site. We encourage you to read our Privacy Policy.

### INDIVIDUAL ACCESS AND CORRECTION

We allow registered users the right to access their personal information using their respective username and password. 

### CHALLENGING COMPLIANCE 

We reserve the right to amend our policies and procedures relating to the handling of personal data to improve the services provided on this website and do have in place mechanisms and processes to receive and address complaints or inquiries about our policies and procedures relating to the handling of personal data. 

Alternatively, complaints may be referred to the ConsumerTrust Secretariat 

The ConsumerTrust Secretariat  
Mr. Ramesh Vakkiprath  
35, Selegie Road, #09-25, Parklane,   
Singapore 188307  
Email: [ramesh@cnsg.com.sg](mailto:ramesh@cnsg.com.sg)  

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Company may revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such revised Privacy Policy on this Web Site (http://www.onemotoring.com.sg). By using this Web Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as outlined in this policy and to the Web Site User Agreement for use of this Web Site.

### OTHER TERMS AND CONDITIONS

See One.motoring Portal Terms and Conditions for use of this Web Site.

### EFFECTIVE DATE

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1 May 2010.

### CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please fill up the feedback form from the Contact Us page.
